本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多美剧下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译： Glory    Nil    zoe    lighthouse    帝释天   时间轴： shawnliu87
校对： Glory  何何  Nil  帝释天   后期： 冰河   总监： 何何
■
前情提要
Previously on 24
联邦调查局
The FBI believes
找到了下一个遇袭目标
they've detected where the next attack will take place.
俄亥俄州汲沦谷镇的化工厂
The chemical plant just outside Kidron, Ohio.
还有多久储气罐会破裂
What's our time frame?
不到15分钟
The tank could rupture in less than 15 minutes.
解决当前危机的唯一方法
Right now our best chance to stop this
就是找到杜巴库和CIP装置
is by finding dubaku and the CIP device.
压力400帕
400 psi.
距储气罐破裂还有多久
How long before the tank ruptures?
7分钟
Seven minutes.
有麻烦了
We've got a problem.
我以为你已经干掉阿尔梅达和杰克了
I thought you killed Almeida and Bauer.
该死  他们怎么找到这的
Damn it! How did they find us?!
我不知道
I don't know!
他们进来了
They're in the building.
解除CIP模块
Disengage the CIP module.
把它卸下来
Begin the offload.
上
Go!
杰克  我拿到CIP装置了
Jack, I've got the CIP device!
已经被破坏了
It's been destroyed.
马托波夫妇很安全  我正带他们上车
The Matobos are safe. I'm taking them to the van.
收到
Copy that.
你和比尔搜那边  看能否找到杜巴库
You and Bill do a sweep. See if you can find Dubaku.
我们无法在百万人口的城市中
We are not equipped to look for one man
找一个人
in a city of millions.
我们需要其它的资源
We need additional resources.
政府吗  他们不可信
The government? They can't be trusted.
我们不能信任任何人
We can't trust anybody.
这就是为什么我们独自行动
That's why we're working on the outside.
可以相信泰勒总统
President Taylor can be trusted.
总统阁下  请您听我讲
Madame president, you need to listen to me.
救我的人拿到了CIP装置
The people who rescued us, they have acquired the CIP device.
它已经被摧毁了
It's being destroyed,
贵国当前的危机已经过去了
And your country's no longer under immediate threat.
他们是谁
Who are these people?
我会当面向您禀告的
I'll tell you everything in person,
但必须是私下里
but I must speak to you alone.
请让亨利接电话
Please get Henry on the phone.
亨利目前无法接通
Henry's unreachable.
我一直在努力联系盖奇探员
I've been trying to reach agent Gedge,
他还是没接电话
And he hasn't picked up.
他说他在萨曼莎·罗斯的公寓外
He said he was outside Samantha Roth's apartment
等候第一先生
waiting for the first gentleman.
你是说我丈夫失踪了吗
You're telling me my husband's gone missing?
盖奇死了
Gedge is dead.
出什么事了
What happened?
出了问题  泰勒杀了盖奇
Something went wrong. Taylor killed Gedge,
我不知道他怎么做到的
I don't know how.
别杀他
Don't kill him.
把他带到我这
Bring him to me.
以下事件发生在下午3点到4点之间
The following take place between 3:00 P.M. and 4:00 P.M.
你确定没被跟踪
You're certain you weren't followed?
是的  快  帮我把他弄进去
Yes. Come on. Help me get him inside.
目前已经确认
We can confirm at this point
发生于华盛顿的空难及俄亥俄州
the tragedies that unfolded in the skies over Washington
汲沦谷镇的悲剧系恐怖分子所为
and in Kidron, Ohio, were indeed acts of terrorism.
但是我向大家保证
But I am here to assure you that those responsible
当前的危机已经过去
are no longer a threat to this country.
他们妄图阻止我们拯救桑加拉的
Their attempts to stop us from intervening
阴谋已经破产
in the Sangalan genocide have failed.
我们不会向恐怖分子屈服
We will not give in to terrorists.
我刚刚下令让军队
A short time ago, I gave the order
开始执行拯救
for our troops to begin operations
桑加拉的军事行动
that will liberate the people of Sangala.
我们有信心在短时间内打垮朱玛政权
We are confident that the Juma regime will collapse swiftly,
桑加拉将在总理
and that democracy will be restored
乌勒·马托波的领导下重获民主
under the leadership of prime minister Ule Motobo.
你  你  过来
You, you, come.
干得好  沃斯勒探员
Well done, agent Vossler.
我得走了
I've got to go now.
我4点钟要换班
I've got a shift that starts at 4:00.
去吧  钱会汇到你指定的账户
Then go. Your money will be wired to the usual account.
房间是隔音的  泰勒先生
The room is soundproof, Mr. Taylor.
放弃徒劳的叫喊和求救吧
There's no point in screaming or trying to call for help.
埃利姆  拿掉泰勒先生的封口布
Elimu, remove Mr. Taylor's gag.
你个狗娘养的
you son of a bitch.
你杀了我儿子
You're behind my son's death.
是他多管闲事自找的
He was poking his nose where it did not belong.
你不会得逞的  清醒点吧
You'll never get away with this. You must know that.
全城的人都在找我
Everyone in the city is going be looking for me.
你只需要回答一个问题  泰勒先生
You should be concerned with just one question, Mr. Taylor.
你妻子对你的爱
Does your wife love you enough
足够让她撤销针对我国的入侵令吗
to call off the invasion of my country?
为了你的性命着想
For your sake,
我希望答案是肯定的
I hope the answer is yes.
激活干扰装置
Activate the scrambling device.
我们的司法机构
Our law enforcement agencies
会将罪魁祸首缉拿归案
will hunt down the people responsible
让他们接受正义的审判
and bring them to justice.
我恳请我们的人民
I ask now that your thoughts and prayers
为死去的同胞及他们的
go to those who lost their lives today,
家人和亲人们祈祷
to their families and loved ones,
并为我们在前线上
and to our troops who are putting their lives
为自由而战的勇士们祈福
on the line in the name of freedom.
谢谢
Thank you.
祝好
Good afternoon.
马托波到了
Motobo's arrived.
他和其他人已经被
He and the others have been brought in secretly
我的心腹手下秘密带到了
through the underground entrance
地下掩体的入口处
by agents I personally know and trust.
马托波告诉我他带来的
Motobo told me the people he's bringing in
这些人救了他的性命
are responsible for saving his life
并且拿回了CIP装置
and recovering the CIP device.
这些人是谁
Who are they?
其中有你认识的前洛杉矶
Bill Buchanan, whom I believe you met
反恐小组的主管比尔·布坎南
when he headed up CTU L.A.,
联邦调查局的探员蕾妮·沃克
FBI agent named Renee Walker
还有杰克·鲍尔
And Jack Bauer.
鲍尔
Bauer...
他不是绑架马托波的元凶之一吗
He was one of Motobo's kidnappers.
这讲不通啊
Doesn't make sense.
我知道
I know.
马托波要求我见见他们
Motobo asked me to listen to what they have to say,
我也正想听听他们的解释
And I'm willing to do so.
让他们进来
Send them in.
总统有请
The president's ready.
乌勒
Ule.
能看到你和阿拉玛
I can't tell you
平安无事真是太好了
how thankful we are that you and Alama are safe.
谢谢  她正和布坎南先生的人在一起
Thank you. She's with Mr. Buchanan's people now,
已经没事了
Recovering.
对于您在我国遭绑架并受辱之事
That you were subjected to such an ordeal
真的让我和我的国家
on our soil is a source of shame both to me
都深感愧疚
personally and to my country.
总统阁下
Madame president,
我更关心的是桑加拉  不是自己
My chief concern is for Sangala, not myself.
我能问一下您
May I ask what your timetable is
何时出兵吗
for the invasion?
我已经下令让部队进攻
I've issued the order To our military to proceed.
真的是太感谢您了
I thank you with all my heart.
您为我的国民所做的
You're doing my people a great service,
和这些人为您国家所做的一样伟大
Much as these people have done for your country.
打断一下  总理先生
Now forgive me, prime minister,
我对这个结果百思不得其解
But I'm finding that hard to believe.
我向您保证  事实不像您想的那样
I assure you, none of this is as it seems.
但他们会解释一切的
But they're here to explain themselves.
现在  请容许我
Now, if you'll excuse me, madame president,
和我的人商议一下
I must meet with my people
战后的重建计划
to discuss post-invasion plans.
当然可以
Of course.
现在马上就给我解释这一切
I want an explanation and I want it now.
到底是怎么回事
What the hell is going on?!
总统阁下
Madame president,
6周前  比尔·布坎南发现
Six weeks ago, Bill Buchanan discovered
您政府内的一个重要成员
that key members of your government
正在同朱玛将军
were working with general Juma
和杜巴库上校合作并试图
and colonel Dubaku in an effort
破坏我国的外交政策
to undermine this nation's foreign policy--
就是您针对桑加拉的出兵计划
Your foreign policy with regards to Sangala.
你们意识到这是一个无端的指控
You realize that that is an outrageous accusation?
是的  阁下
Yes, ma'am.
不幸的是  这是事实
Unfortunately, it's the truth.
这就是在这次危机中您针对
It explains why during this crisis,
杜巴库所做的一切努力都失败的原因
Every effort you made to stop Dubaku failed.
比尔  为什么你不告诉我
Bill, why didn't you come to me?
我不知道该相信谁也不知道您能否相信我
I didn't know who I could trust or if you'd even believe me.
所以我安插了
So I formed
一个小组来找出杜巴库
a small group to locate and neutralize Dubaku.
最终托尼·阿尔梅达和杰克
Tony Almeida and ultimately, Jack,
加入了我们
Joined me.
起先就是托尼·阿尔梅达
Tony Almeida was the one who put the CIP device
把CIP装置
into Dubaku's hands
卖给杜巴库的
in the first place.
利用CIP装置做诱饵  对卧底工作
Using the CIP device as bait was necessary
是很必要的
to the undercover operation.
我们能利用它引出杜巴库
We had to follow it back to Dubaku.
那么多的人
A lot of people
死于空难  更别说汲沦谷的
died on those planes, never mind what
化工厂还有发生泄露的危险
could have happened at the chemical plant in Kidron!
总统阁下  打断一下
Madame president, if I may, I was part
我参与了联调局追回CIP装置的行动
of the FBI task force assigned to recover the CIP device,
我以个人名义担保他们所说的话
and I can personally vouch for what they're telling you.
的确  很多人牺牲了
The loss of life was tragic, yes,
但是在我看来
but in my opinion,everything
这些人所做的  却拯救了成千上万的人
these men have done saved the lives of thousands.
假设你们所说的是事实
If I choose to believe everything you're telling me,
你们下一步打算怎么办
where would you go from here?
杜巴库是唯一知道
Dubaku is the only person
在政府里面
with the names of the people who betrayed you
都有谁背叛了您
within your government.
我们必须找到他
It's imperative that we find him.
我们必须暗中调查
We would have to work under the radar.
一旦声张出去
Any word of an investigation,
他们就会躲藏起来
people would start running for cover.
你是说  联邦调查局和国土安全局
You're saying we can't even involve
也不能包括在内
The FBI and homeland?
是的  长官
Yes, sir, That's correct.
总统阁下
Madame president,
蒂姆·伍兹找您
Tim Woods is on the phone.
他说情况紧急
He says it's urgent.
接过来
Put him through.
请坐吧
Have a seat.
喂
Yes?
总统阁下  抱歉打扰
Madame president, I'm sorry to interrupt.
埃克·杜巴库打电话来了
There's a call for you from Ike Dubaku.
声音对比确定是他  他说是关于您丈夫的
Voice I.D. confirms that. He says it's about your husband.
我丈夫
My husband?
是的  阁下  我为您接通
Yes, ma'am. I'll connect you.
我是泰勒总统
This is president Taylor.
开门见山吧  总统阁下
I'll come straight to the point, madame president.
你丈夫在我手里
I have your husband.
给你证明下
Let me demonstrate.
打个招呼
Say something.
艾莉森
Allison...
亨利  你没事吧
Henry, are you all right?
我没事
I'm fine.
对不起
I'm sorry about this.
看在上帝的份上  别让他们利用我
For god sake, don't let them use me
来影响你做任何决定
to influence you in any way.
我的要求如下
My demands as follows
立即下令让你的军队
You will have your forces
从我的国家桑加拉
withdrawn from around my country, Sangala,
永久撤军
immediately and permanently.
另外  把马托波交给我的人
Also, Motobo must be delivered to my men
他们会在斯坦威克
who will be stationed at the east lot
发电厂的东侧空地等着
of the stanswick power plant.
四点之前  不把他交出来
If he's not there by 4:00,
或者想跟踪或阻止我的人
or if anybody attempts to follow or impede my men
离开发电厂
when they leave the plant,
你丈夫会被慢慢折磨致死
your husband will die a slow and certain death.
你敢
You wouldn't dare!
切掉他的手指
Cut off his finger.
住手
Stop it!
满足我的要求
Meet my demands
不然  我会把他切成块儿  给你送回去
or I will send him back to you one piece at a time.
明白了么  总统阁下
Do you understand, madame president?
好的 我明白了
Yes, I understand.
任何想找到你丈夫的尝试
Any attempt to find your husband
我都会很快知道的
will be known to me very quickly,
然后我会马上杀了他
And I will kill him immediately.
总统阁下  我刚得知
Madame president, I just heard back
派出去的人员  在亨利最后一个落脚点
from the team I sent to Henry's last-known location.
发现了萨曼莎·罗斯
They found Samantha Roth's
和盖奇探员的尸体
and secret service agent Gedge's bodies.
天哪
Oh, god!
盖奇持有令人瘫痪的药物
Gedge had possession of a paralytic drug.
证据表明  盖奇与人合谋
That and other evidence on scene suggests he was complicit
绑架了亨利  当然  这也证明了
in Henry's abduction, which, of course, confirms
你们刚刚提到的腐败问题
the corruption you just told us about.
总统阁下  时间紧迫
Madame president, time is tight.
我们得马上做出反应
We need to decide how to respond.
没人会指责您
I don't think anyone would blame you
停止  哪怕是暂时的
for holding back, at least temporarily,
对桑加拉的进攻
the invasion of Sangala.
空难总共死了多少人
How many people died on those planes?
多少
How many?!
大概三百人  阁下
About 300, ma'am.
都是因为我坚持进兵桑加拉
All because I refused to change course in Sangala.
怎么可以只叫美国人民做出牺牲
How can I ask the American people to make sacrifices
而我却例外呢
That I'm not willing to make myself?
我不能屈服
I can't give in.
绝不
I can't.
总统阁下
Madame president...
四点之前我们还是
We can still try and find your husband
有希望救出您丈夫的
before the 4:00 deadline.
杜巴库明令禁止这么做
Dubaku has specifically forbidden that.
而且根据你的说法
And according to you, I can't trust any of my
我无法相信任何执法机构
law enforcement agencies.
您可以相信我
You can trust me.
现在所有人都认为沃克探员已经死了
Right now everyone believes that agent Walker is dead,
我也没有任何身份
And I have no status at all.
这就意味着  杜巴库的内线
Which means that Dubaku's spies
无法追踪我们  就官方的说法  我们并不存在
cannot track us because officially, we don't exist.
你已经辞去了公职
You resigned from government service,
参议院也把你定性为叛国者
And the senate regards you as having been a renegade agent.
这叫我如何相信你呢
How am I supposed to know where your loyalties really lie?
总统阁下  您可以打听我的为人
With all due respect, madame president, ask around.
这么短的时间  你们又能做什么呢
What could you even do on such short notice?
我不敢承诺什么
I couldn't make you any promises,
但是我会全力以赴救出您丈夫
But we will do everything possible to save your husband.
现在我们需要您假装
Right now, we need you to go along
屈服于杜巴库的要求  帮我们争取时间
with Dubaku's demands. Help buy us some time.
总统阁下  您没有别的选择了
Madame president, you don't have another choice.
好吧
All right.
拜托你找到他
Find him, please?
好的  阁下
Yes, ma'am.
我们需要条绝密线路
We're gonna need a secure hard line.
如果需要  你们可以用这间屋
You may use this room if you need to.
准备好时  我会派人
I'll have you escorted back out through
护送你们从地下出口出去
The underground entrance when you're ready.
我需要一份总统和第一先生的
I'm gonna need a copy of the president
特勤人员的详细资料
and the first gentleman's secret service details.
我让他们给你拿一份
I'll have them brought to you.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们从盖奇探员开始
Okay, we'll start off with agent Gedge.
我们得查他的通话记录
We need access to his phone records.
我要知道  过去几小时他跟谁通过话
I want to know who he's been talking to over the last few hours.
很明显  这事我们无法
Obviously, we can't use any of
通过总统的安保人员得知
The president's security people.
谢谢
Thank you.
通话记录是高级机密
Phone logs are highly classified,
尤其是保护总统家庭的探员的
Especially for agents assigned to the first family.
克罗伊能破解进去么
Can Chloe o'brian get access?
找一个有权查看的
It'll be faster if we can get someone
会更快一些
Who's already got clearance.
拉里·莫斯
Larry Moss.
他可不像能在
He doesn't strike me
背地里干活的人
as someone who's willing to work outside the system.
的确  但是我能说服他帮我们
That's true, but I think I can persuade him to do what we need.
你真的相信他
You really trust him?
是的  我们彼此很了解
Yes. we know each other pretty well.
好  试试吧  我们时间不多了
Fine. Try him. We don't have much time.
我是莫斯探员
Agent Moss.
拉里  我是蕾妮  我还活着
Larry, it's Renee. I'm alive,
不要告诉任何人  明白么
But you can't let anyone know. Do you understand me?
天哪
Oh, my god.
蕾妮  你在哪呢  你没事吧
Renee? What... where are you? are you all right?
我没事  待会再跟你解释
I'm-I'm fine. I'll explain later,
现在我们需要你的帮助
But right now we need your help.
我们  还有谁
Who's, who's "we"?
我和杰克·鲍尔
Myself and Jack Bauer.
什么
What?!
他站在我们这边  拉里  像他说的
He's on our side, Larry, just like he said.
他做的一切只是不想暴露自己
Everything that he did, he did to preserve his cover.
蕾妮  这么长时间  我都在担心你的生死
Renee, this whole time I've been thinking you were dead.
你为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
拉里  如他所言
The bureau is compromised.
调查局有内鬼  这是一次
Larry, just like he said, and no one there can know
机密行动  而且不能留下记录
about this operation. It has to stay completely off book.
什么行动
What operation?
我和杰克在白宫
Jack and I are at the white house.
第一先生被杜巴库绑架了
The first gentleman has been kidnapped by ike Dubaku.
我...  我完全不知情
I don't, I don't know anything about that.
真的  总统命令我和杰克找到他
It's true. The president's asked Jack and me to find him.
只有几人知晓此事
Very few people know about this,
我们必须守口如瓶  掩人耳目
and that's the way that it has to stay.
要是我们4点还找不到他  他就会被杀
If we don't find him by 4:00 p.m., he'll be killed.
拉里  如果你曾相信过我
Larry... if you've ever trusted me,
现在也请相信我吧  帮帮我
trust me now, please, and help me.
要我怎么帮
What do you want me to do?
好像第一先生的特勤局保镖
Looks like the first gentleman's secret service agent
与此事有关  他叫布莱恩·盖奇  他死了
was involved in all of this-- Brian Gedge; he's dead.
查查他的电话记录
You need to check his phone logs
并尽可能拿到他的
and get all the information you can
近期所有的通话记录
about who he's been in contact with recently.
我得见你  确定这一切是真的
I need to see you to make sure this is real,
不是你在受到胁迫下说出来的
that you're not under duress.
没有那么做的时间了
No, there's no time for that.
没得商量  要我帮忙  就和我见面
That's not negotiable. You want my help, we meet.
在静思池见  尽快赶到
The capitol reflecting pool, as soon as you can get there.
好吧
Okay, fine.
我想他会帮我们  但我们得过去
He'll help us, I think, but we need to go.
泰勒总统强调
President Taylor emphasized
恐怖分子不再是威胁
the terrorists are no longer a threat
并将开始进军
and says the invasion will begin.
她还说
She also says
前总理乌勒·马托波会重新上台
former prime minister Ule Motobo will be reinstated
并建立一个新的民主政府
to work towards building a new democratic government.
我不明白
I don't get it.
怎么
What?
总统这么说  好像
The president's talking as if
已经找到CIP装置和马托波了似的
the CIP device and Motobo have been recovered,
但如果这是真的  我们怎么不知道
but how could that have happened without us knowing about it?
那只能说明别的局把这事儿办了
Well, it just means whatever agency's responsible
没告诉我们
hasn't let us know.
还有别的局吗
What other agency?
我们都被蒙在鼓里了
We're being kept out of the loop,
我不喜欢这样
and I don't like it.
今晚我们有"节目"吗
So am I seeing you later?
不知道  我还有事要处理
I don't know. I've got some things to figure out.
你什么意思
What does that mean?
我是说我得回家一趟
It means I have to get home at some point.
我都一周没见克里斯蒂娜了
I haven't seen Christina in a week.
好吧
All right.
西恩  你还好吧
Sean, are you all right?
我还好
I'm fine.
我觉得你在疏远我
I'm sensing a little distance.
我得继续干活了
I just have to get back to work.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
拜托别做得这么露骨  行吗
Could you be a little less obvious, do you think?
你指什么
What are you talking about?
得了吧
Give me a break.
你干脆举个牌子  写上
Just hold up a sign that says,
嘿  同志们  我们有一腿
"hey, world, we're sleeping together."
你是傻子吗
Are you stupid?
我知道这是个愚蠢的错误
I know it's stupid and wrong,
我会了断这一切
and I'm gonna end it.
对  最好快一点  别让拉里觉察
Yeah, you'd better, fast, before Larry notices.
拉里人呢
Where is Larry?
我不知道  这不重要
I don't know. That's not the point.
重要的是  要是他发现了
The point is, if he finds out about this,
他会立马把你这混蛋打发到朱诺市
he's gonna transfer your ass to juneau so fast,
整得你晕头转向
your head will spin.
拉里
Larry.
我的上帝
Oh, my god.
我还以为再也见不到你了
I thought I'd never see you again.
你能否得到盖奇探员的电话记录
Were you able to access agent Gedge's phone records?
能
Yeah.
我能
Yeah,
在之前的三个小时  盖奇和另一个
over the last three hours, Gedge spoke repeatedly
探员保持密切联系  他叫爱德华·沃斯勒
to another secret service agent named Edward Vossler.
我查了沃斯勒的个人档案
I checked out Vossler's personnel records.
担任特勤局探员以前  他在特种部队
Before he was a secret service agent,he was special forces
并在桑加拉服役两年
and for two years, served in Sangala.
那我们可以假设沃斯勒为杜巴库效命
So we can assume Vossler's working for Dubaku.
有没有带着这些文件
Did you bring any of his files with you?
带了
Yeah.
沃斯勒有家人吗
Does vossler have a family?
你问这个干嘛
Why do you need to know that?
他有没有家人
Does he have a family?
他五年前娶了个律师助手
He's been married for five years to a paralegal.
并生有一个11月大的小男孩
They have an 11-month-old baby boy.
她辞了工作在家带孩子
She left her job to stay home with the kid.
好  我们要分头行动了
Okay, we're gonna need to split up.
我要你去跟踪沃斯勒
I need you to help me track Vossler.
你去他家  找到他的家人
I need you to go to his home and hope his family is there.
沃斯勒曾是特种兵
Vossler was special forces.
这么短的时间  我们无法撬开他的嘴
There's no way we're gonna break him in the time that we've got.
要让他合作  我们只能让他认为
The only way to get him to cooperate is to make him
我们会伤及他的老婆孩子
think we're gonna hurt his family, his wife and his kid.
不  绝对不行  蕾妮
No, absolutely not. Renee?
那样做有些过火了  杰克
That's stepping over the line, Jack.
你审问坦纳的时候
You stepped over the line
也很过火
the second you interrogated tanner.
坦纳是个杀人犯
Tanner's a murderer.
而目前看来  沃斯勒的妻子完全是无辜的
As far as we know, Vossler's wife is completely innocent,
更不用说一个小娃娃了
let alone a small child.
你们这些家伙什么时候能不再
When are you people gonna stop thinking
痴心妄想地认为世人都会循规蹈矩呢
everyone else is following your rules?!
他们不会
They're not!
杜巴库会在45分钟内
Dubaku is gonna kill Henry Taylor
杀了亨利·泰勒  除非我们找到他
within the next 45 minutes unless we find him.
有两条路摆在你面前
You got to have one of two choices.
要么你可以打电话给总统  向她解释
Now you can either phone the president and explain to her
你的良知不允许你
that your conscience won't allow you
采取必要手段去救他
to do what is necessary to save him,
要么就采取必要手段去做该做的事
Or you can simply do what is necessary.
选一个吧
Pick one!
蕾妮
Renee?
拉里
Larry!
蕾妮
Renee?
我要用你的车
I'm gonna need your vehicle.
利用特工的专用网络
Start tracking Vossler through his cell phone.
通过手机追踪沃斯勒
Utilize his secret service deployment grid.
看看你自己吧
Look at yourself.
因为去做你认为该做的事情
You've lost everyone and everything you ever had
你已经失去了一切
by doing what you think is necessary.
我不会让她步你的后尘  鲍尔
I won't let you do it to her, Bauer.
蕾妮不会和你一个下场的
Renee will not end up like you.
你到底给不给我车钥匙
Are you gonna give me your keys or not?
杰克
Jack.
Jack!
规则都是为我们好
The rules are what make us better.
今天不是
Not today.
即使是那些反对进军桑加拉的人
Even those who oppose the plan to invade Sangala
也无法否认朱玛政权的暴行
can't deny the atrocities committed by that regime.
我减缓了泰勒出血的速度
I slowed down Taylor's bleeding,
但不能完全止血
but I can't get it to stop completely.
止血绷带已经是最紧了吗
Tourniquet is as tight as possible?
是的
Yes.
那就通过灼烧伤口止血吧
Then cauterize the wound.
米卡利有焊枪
Mikali has a blowtorch.
泰勒会休克的
You risk Taylor going into shock.
把他的嘴塞住
Just put something in his mouth.
我可不想他因为疼痛把舌头咬掉
I don't want him biting his tongue off with the pain.
你在家干什么呢
Hey, what are you doing at home, huh?
我以为你在上班呢
I thought you'd be at work.
刚刚是  但在餐馆时罗莎给我打电话
I was. Rosa called me at the diner.
她又给我讲她的大道理了
She was having one of her episodes.
你知道你姐的  她只想操控你
You know your sister. She's just manipulating you.
你不必每次都随叫随到
You don't have to go to her every time she calls.
我是她的依靠  萨缪尔  对她好点儿
I'm all she has, Samuel. Be kind.
你知道  你对我们都很好
You know, you're kind enough for both of us.
我只想确认一下
I just wanted to make sure
你今晚会不会回来吃饭
that you were still coming to dinner tonight.
抱歉  我去不了
Um, look, I'm really sorry, but I can't.
我手头有一堆运单
I'm looking at a stack of shipping manifests.
不是吧  就不能想想办法吗
Oh, no! Isn't there some way?
你想多晚吃都可以的
We could do it as late as you want.
我也希望我能
I really wish I could.
对不起  玛丽卡
I'm sorry, Marika.
听着  宝贝
Uh, listen, baby,
我会补偿你的  好吗
I'll make it up to you, okay?
好吧  我还是会多做些菜
Okay. Well, I'm gonna make extra
以防你改变主意
just in case you change your mind.
你对我太好了
You're too good to me.
你说对了
You're right.
我得回餐馆去了  罗莎
I have to get back to the diner, rosa.
你还好吧
Are you gonna be okay?
你刚才和谁通话
Who was that on the phone?
是他吗
It was him, wasn't it?
行了
All right, stop.
我知道你不喜欢塞缪尔
I know you don't approve
但我爱他
of Samuel, but I love him.
你爱他
Oh. You love him?
为什么
Why?
因为他出手大方
Because he spends money on you?
因为他帮我们付房租
Because he pays our rent?
你和他认识不过
You've only known him
才四个月
four months.
难道这真的很重要吗
What difference does that make?
你根本不了解他
You don't know anything about him.
他真如自己口口声声所说是进口商么
What if he's not the importer he says he is?
万一是个偷渡客呢
Or that he's in this country illegally?
你又来了
Not this again.
我只想保护你  玛丽卡
I'm just trying to protect you, Marika.
我需要你的保护
I don't need your protection.
你需要
Yes, you do.
这个人不是
This man isn't...
不是什么
Isn't what?
没什么
Nothing.
算了
Forget it.
对不起  我没时间讨论这个
I'm sorry, I don't have time for this.
轮班后我再回来
I'll be home after my shift.
我们可以假意顺从杜巴库的第一个要求
We can appear to comply with the first part of Dubaku's demand
让舰队后撤
by pulling the fleet back.
然后我们再从外海发起攻击
Then we simply launch the invasion from farther out at sea.
他的第二个要求有点麻烦
Now, the second part of his demand is more complicated.
如果我们真要交出马托波
If we were really turning Matobo over,
他现在应该在车上了
We'd be putting him in a car right about now.
这不可能  我们要保护他
That's out of the question. We need him safe.
的确  但我们可以找个替身
Agreed. But we can send a car with a look-alike.
顺利的话  杜巴库到最后时刻
If we handle it right, Dubaku won't be aware of the deception
才会察觉到
until the last minute.
那时我们可能已经找到亨利了
By then, hopefully, we'll have found Henry.
总统阁下  您同意这么做吗
Madame president,do we have your authorization to proceed?
好吧
Yes.
我是鲍尔
This is Bauer.
我找到沃斯勒了  他在环路上
Okay, I've got Vossler. He's on the beltway
在贝塞斯达附近  向南行进  距你7英里
Near Bethesda, moving south, about seven miles from you.
收到  我正赶往  他要去哪
Copy that. I'm on my way. Where's he headed?
特勤局纪录显示
According to the secret service log,
他在4点换班
his shift starts at 4:00 p.m.
他要到安德鲁斯去机场接某位国外高官
He's meeting a foreign dignitary's plane at Andrews.
杰克  你知道
Jack, I don't have to tell you--
他一旦到了那
Once he's through that gate and onto that base,
你就动不了他了
you're not going to be able to touch him.
他要到达那里  得在337号路上
Okay, he's going to have to double back on the 337
折返两次
if he wants to get through that main gate.
我走康乃狄格路应该能赶上他
I should be able to make up time by taking connecticut.
帮我盯住他
Just keep sight of him.
蕾妮给你打电话了吗
have you heard from Renee?
她到了沃斯勒家吗
Do we know if she's arrived at Vossler's house yet?
没  但如果她有麻烦
No. But she knows how to get in touch with us
会联系我们的
if she's in trouble.
来了
Coming.
有事吗
Can I help you?
你是谁
Who are you?
闭嘴  照我说的做
Shut up. Do what I tell you, and there's a chance
就饶你们不死
you'll live through this.
-别动  -他吓坏了
- Don't move!  - He's scared.
别动  不然我就开枪
Stay where you are or I will shoot you where you stand.
我看一眼孩子就要杀我吗
You're going to kill me for trying to comfort my baby?
坐下
Sit down.
你还是人吗
What kind of a person are you?
就这样对我们
Doing this to us.
你应该问你丈夫
You should ask your husband that.
什么意思
What are you talking about?
爱德华是个好人
Edward is a good man.
也许你还不够了解他
Maybe you don't know him quite as well as you think you do.
-他不会用枪指着小孩  -闭嘴
- I know he would never point a gun near a child.  - Shut up!
把自己铐上
Put the cuff around your wrist.
别这样
Don't do this.
快点
Now!
他现在到哪了
Okay, where is he now?
刚下环路
He just got off the beltway.
他停下来了
He's stopped in traffic.
我在赶往艾伦福德和奥斯的
Okay, I'm coming up on the intersection
十字路口  30秒后到
of allenford and auth. I should be there in 30 seconds.
他车开了就告诉我
Just let me know if he moves.
他车开了
he's moving.
该死
Damn it!
北边下条街是什么
What's the next street north?
百特路
Baxter drive.
不过这是条单行道  杰克
But, Jack, it's a one-way street.
收到
Copy that.
他过了艾伦福德的红绿灯了
He made the light at allenford.
我在百特路上
I'm on baxter.
离你15秒  杰克
He's 15 seconds away, Jack.
10秒
Ten seconds.
5秒
Five seconds.
看到他了
I got him.
举起手来
Let me see your hands!
马上
Now!
下车  下车
Get out of the car. Get out of the car!
走  走
Move. Move!
他在哪
Where is he?
-亨利·泰勒在哪  -我不知道你在说什么
- Where is Henry Taylor?  - I don't know what you're talking about.
他在哪里
Where is he?
好吧
Fine,
是你逼我们的
We'll do this your way.
喂
Yes.
我抓到沃斯勒了  抓到他老婆了
I've got Vossler. You got his wife?
-还有他孩子  -准备好了吗
- And his child.  - You ready?
嗯
Yes.
打开免提
Put your phone on speaker.
和你老婆讲话
Talk to your wife.
-你个狗娘养的  -和她讲话
- You son of a bitch...  - Talk to your wife!
卡罗尔  你没事吧
Carol, ar-are you all right?
这有个拿枪的女人威胁要杀我
There's a woman with a gun. She's threatening to kill me.
康纳怎么哭了
Why is Conner crying?
我的上帝  爱德华
Oh, my god, Edward.
出什么事了  他们是谁
What's happening? Who are these people?
你没时间了
You are running out of time.
别逼我做不想做的事
I didn't want to have to do this.
不  不要
No, you wouldn't...
-怎么了  -我不知道  康纳在她手上
- What's happening?  - I don't know. she's got conner.
我的天  她对康纳下手了
Oh, my god, She's doing something to conner!
别动我孩子
Let go of my baby!
他只是个孩子  求你了
He's just a baby! Please!
-你们在做什么  -说出来我们就收手
- What the hell are you doing?- You can stop this. Just tell me where he is.
上帝啊  爱德华  快说啊
For god's sake, Edward, tell them what they want to know!
该死  好  好  我说
Damn it! All right, all right, I'll tell you!
停下  我一会打给你
Stand down. I'll get back to you.
你的孩子没事
Your baby's fine.
你这个恶魔
You're a monster!
他在哪里
Where is he?!
不说的话  别怪我
You tell me now, or the situation
对你家人不客气
for your family goes from bad to worse.
他在哪里
Where is he?
我说了难道你就不杀他们
How do I know you're just not going to kill them anyway?
你没得选择
You don't.
好吧
Fine.
在一个杂货店  阿林顿大街12451号
There's a greengrocer, 12451 arlington avenue.
他被关在地下室
They're holding him in the basement.
入口
Access.
后面有个楼梯
There's a staircase in the back,
但一般是锁着的
but it's always locked.
-杜巴库也在吗  -是的
- Is Dubaku with him?  - He was.
有几个看守
How many guns are guarding him?
-至少4个  -滚开
- At least four.  - Get out of here!
离我车远点
Get away from the car!
滚开  马上
Walk away... now!
该死
Damn it.
停车
Stop!
下车
Get out of the car now!
快点  快点
Move! Move!
行动目的是让我们看上去在交出
The goal is to make it look like we're going to hand Matobo over
马托波  并尽可能拖延时间
for as long as is reasonably possible.
你到了约定地点后 和敌人保持距离
When you get to the rendezvous point, keep your distance from dubaku's men.
让他们看到你在后座
Let them see you in the backseat,
但别下车
but do not get out of the car.
别让他们靠得太近
Don't let them get any closer than you feel comfortable with.
如果情况不对 马上走人
As soon as you start to feel that the risk is unacceptable, get the hell out.
-这是总统的指示明白吗  -明白
That's straight from the president. Clear?  - clear.
祝你们好运
Good luck.
杰克
Jack?
我查到了
I got an address
亨利·泰勒的地址  阿林顿大街12451号
For henry taylor. 12451 arlington avenue.
是个杂货店  他被关在地下室
It's a storefront. he's being held in the basement.
要是你先到  先别贸然行动
If you get there before I do, I want you to stand down.
杜巴库安排了至少4个武装分子守在那
Dubaku's got at least four gunmen there.
-好的  -我会打电话给比尔
All right. meanwhile, I'm going to call bill,
给他通告下目前的情况
Pull him up to speed.
你同样也去通知拉里
I want you to do the same thing with larry.
-沃斯勒呢  -死了
And what about vossler? he's dead.
他进行了反抗  我别无选择
He attacked me. I didn't have a choice.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
不  不好
No, I don't think I am.
什么意思  怎么了
What do you mean? what's wrong?
沃克探员  你在听吗
Agent walker, are you still there?
我不...
I'm not...
听我说
Listen to me.
我们能走到这一步  多亏了你
We could not have gotten this far if it wasn't for you.
懂吗
Okay?
你承受得太多了
No one would blame you
没人会为此责怪你的
if this was just too much for you to handle.
也许你不该干这行
Maybe you should get out.
也许吧
Maybe I will.
好吧
Yeah.
等明天再说吧
Tomorrow.
迈森探员和我已经上路了
Agent masden and I are on our way.
我们会通过卫星追踪你们
We'll be tracking you via satellite.
接近发电厂就向我报告
Check in with me when you're approaching the power plant.
遵命  长官
Yes, sir.
你觉得这能为我们争取多少时间
How much time do you think this will buy us?
可以拖延到杜巴库发现马托波不在车里
Until dubaku realizes matobo's not in the limo.
10分钟吧  也许15分钟
Ten minutes, maybe 15.
这又为我们争取了15分钟
That's 15 minutes more than we had.
总统阁下  我刚和杰克·鲍尔通过电话
Madame president, I just got off the phone with jack bauer.
他和沃克探员知道你丈夫在哪了
He and agent walker think they have a location on your husband.
在哪
Where?
阿林顿大街  他们在路上了
Arlington avenue. they're on their way now.
多久能赶到
How long will it take them?
10到15分钟
Ten, 15 minutes.
谢谢
Thank you.
这是刚从国土安全局发来的
This just came over from homeland.
就像你说的
Like you said--
我们都被蒙在鼓里了
We're being kept out of the loop.
谢谢
Thanks.
你看到吗
Did you see this?
国土安全局准备降低警戒等级
Homeland's preparing to lower the threat level
总统亲自下的令
At the president's request.
对  我看到更新的通知了
Yeah, I saw the flash.
你不觉得很奇怪吗
Don't you think that's odd,
我们竟全然不知已找到CIP装置
Considering we don't know anything about the cip device being recovered?
对  我会和国土安全局谈一下
Yeah. I'll talk to homeland.
我说的是  我觉得
All I'm saying is... I get the feeling
好像有人背着我们暗中行事
Like there's something going on behind our back here.
像我说的  我会和他们谈的
Like I said, I'll talk to them.
-失陪  -好的
Excuse me. yeah, sure.
你在哪
Where are you?
正在去亨利·泰勒被关的地方
On my way to where we think henry taylor's being held.
看来你们让沃斯勒招供了
So you got vossler to talk.
我们只有一线希望救出总统的丈夫
It gave us our only chance to rescue the president's husband.
地址是什么
What's the address?
我会派特警组与你们会合
I'll send a swat team to meet you.
你知道你不能那么做
You know you can't do that.
调查局有内鬼
The bureau's compromised.
这会让我们所有的努力功亏一篑
It will jeopardize any attempt that we make.
但我有别的事要你做
But there is something else I need you to do.
好  什么事
Okay, what's that?
对一件事守口如瓶
Keep an incident quiet
直到我和杰克搞定一切
Until what jack and I are doing goes down.
什么事
What incident?
沃斯勒死了
Vossler's dead.
杰克在第18街和里根街路口的酒店杀了他
Jack killed him at the hotel on 18th and riggin.
他是正当防卫
It was self-defense.
他就是这么糊弄你的吗
Is that what he told you?
-拉里  -该死  蕾妮  你和他到底想干嘛
Larry... damn it, renee, what the hell are you doing with this guy?
我们应将嫌犯捉拿归案  而不是取人性命
We're supposed to bring suspects in, not murder them.
拉里  求你了
Larry, please...
在我们查出杜巴库的内线之前
And until we know who dubaku's source is there,
你得摆脱调查局单干了  好吗
You've got to handle this outside of the bureau, okay?
我在特区警局里有个哥们
There's a guy at d.c. metro I know I can trust.
我让他善后沃斯勒的事
I'll have him deal with vossler.
谢谢你  拉里
Thank you, larry.
明白  我会告诉他的
I understand. I will let him know.
我们的线人说  马托波刚刚坐车
According to our sources, a vehicle containing matobo
-离开了白宫  -很好
Just left the white house. good.
美军目前的情况如何
What is the state of the american invasion forces?
舰队正在从
The fleet is withdrawing
桑加拉的领海撤退
From sangalan territorial waters,
已退至23度子午线
And has set its team for the 23rd meridian.
太好了
Excellent.
喂
Hello.
我是罗莎
It's rosa.
罗莎  你要找玛丽卡的话  她不在我身边
Rosa, if you're looking for marika, she's not with me.
我找的是你  塞缪尔
I'm looking for you, samuel.
或许这不是你的真名
Or whatever your real name is.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
我妹妹也许很单纯  但我不傻
My sister may be naive, but I'm not.
我从一个移民局的朋友那打听到
I checked with someone I know at immigration services,
无论是去年还是过去的15年里  都没有叫
And no one named samuel aboa emigrated from sangala
塞缪尔·安博的人从桑加拉移民过来
In the last year, or in the last 15 years.
很显然他们弄错了
Well, they've obviously made a mistake.
是你错了
You're making a mistake.
我不想知道你究竟是谁  也不在乎
Now I don't know who you really are, and I don't care.
我只想让你远离我妹妹
I just want you out of my sister's life.
玛丽卡知道这些吗
Does marika know about this?
还没
No, not yet.
她还是不知情的好
And I'm willing to keep it that way.
你没有向任何人举报我吗
So you've not reported me to anyone?
没有  我不想玛丽卡知道这事
No. I don't want marika to know anything about this.
你想怎样
What do you want?
和她分手
Break up with her,
我就保证不说出去
And this stays between us.
今晚就分手
You just end it tonight,
我们就井水不犯河水
And we won't have a problem.
我得去处理个小麻烦
I have to take care of a little problem.
一抓到马托波就通知我
Call me when we have matobo.
请讲
Yeah.
载着马托波的车
The vehicle that's supposed to be delivering matobo
快到达发电厂了  稍有迟疑
Is arriving at the power plant. if we delay any longer,
杜巴库就会生疑  你那情况怎样
Dubaku is going to get suspicious. what's your status?
-我快到了  还能争取多少时间  -不知道  杰克
I'm almosthere. how much time can you buy us? I dot know, jack.
好  我一到就和沃克探员进去
Okay, agent walker and I will move in as soon as I get there.
我会随时向你汇报
I'll keep you posted.
好的  祝你好运
All right, good luck.
我是史密斯探员
this is agent smith.
-我们看到了杜巴库的人了  -收到
We've got a visual on dubaku's men. understood.
使用卫星画面监控
We have it on satellite.
把他交给我们
Bring him to us.
他们命令我们下车
They've ordered us to get out of the car.
-一个人在打电话  -再坚持一会  探员
Now one of them is making a call. hang tight, agent.
他们的车到了
Their car arrived,
-但是没有动静  -没有动静是什么意思
But nothing is happening. what do you mean nothing is happening?
我们让他们把马托波交给我们
We ordered them to hand matobo over to us
但是没人下车
But no one's getting out of the vehicle.
美国佬耍了我们
The americans have been playing us.
轰了他们的车
Destroy their vehicle.
是  长官
Yes, sir.
-时间太久了  叫他们撤离  -撤退
-That's long enough. get them the hell out of there. -retreat.
-立即撤离  -收到
Get out now. roger that.
-准备好了吗  -好了
You ready? yes.
我们走
Let's go.
从柜台后面出来  快  出来
Get out from behind the counter. now! move!
好  把门打开
Okay, I want you to unlock that door.
然后问那些人想吃什么
And I want you to ask those men what they want to eat.
要是你胆敢乱来
You do one thing I don't like,
我就让你脑袋开花  懂吗
And I will blow your head off, you understand me?
开门
Open the door.
需要什么吃的吗
want anything to eat?
-不了  来点冰啤酒  -好的
No. some cold beers. okay.
喂
Yes.
杀了亨利·泰勒
Kill henry taylor.
那我们就没有威胁他们的筹码了
Then we have nothing to hold over their heads.
我们已经没有了
We don't have anything now.
总统已不管他的死活
The president was willing to let him die.
我们没戏了
We are done here.
杀了泰勒
Kill taylor,
让你的人收拾好一切
And have your men pack everything up.
明白
Understood.
我的上帝
Oh, my god.
先生  先生
sir... sir...
我们会救你的
We're going to get you help.
坚持住
Just stay with me.
快叫救护车
Get an ambulance!